soulcams.com 2011-04-11

# Privacy Policy. WildOrchidz.com - Adult Video Chat, Webcam Girls, Live Sex, Sex Webcams, XXX Chat

**soulcams.com Privacy Policy**

**soulcams.com** is committed to maintaining a privacy policy that benefits each individual customer's preferences we protect your privacy!!!

   This policy explains the privacy practices for soulcams.com (hereinafter referred "soulcams.com", "site", "our", "we", or "us"). In order to provide interactive computer billing and fraud services, soulcams.com collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with soulcams.com in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use. 

**       Information Collection: **

   Visitors can access our Web site home page and browse our Web site without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, soulcams.com may request that you voluntarily supply soulcams.com with primary personal data (such as name and email address) and identifiers (such as web site password). soulcams.com gives you the option of using a secure transmission method of sending such information. 

   soulcams.com receives and stores all information that you enter in our Web site and billing pages. In addition, soulcams.com collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address, and soulcams.com employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. However, we do not collect information from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. You are required to provide soulcams.com with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide soulcams.com with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with soulcams.com. 

   You can inquire about your personal data by sending an e-mail to support@soulcams.com. Prior to completing your request, soulcams.com may require that you provide soulcams.com with proof of your identity. soulcams.com reserves the right to refuse any request for information though soulcams.com will communicate the reason for its decision. 

**       Information Use: **

   soulcams.com is the sole owner of the information collected on it site. soulcams.com will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed it this policy. soulcams.com shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement or the contract rights of its clients. soulcams.com shares the following data with the owner/operator of the web site from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing soulcams.com services: the URL you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your name, your address, your phone number, your date of birth, and your agreement to be bound by soulcams.com terms and conditions. soulcams.com uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Web site, research and development, and fraud deterrence.

**       Email correspondence: **

    soulcams.com may request a confirmation when you receive and open and e-mail communication delivered by soulcams.com. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network.

**       Information sharing: **

   We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to governmental institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**       Third party information: **

    Occasionally, soulcams.com receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to soulcams.com for fraud prevention purposes. 

**       Security: **

   We date every protection to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss. soulcams.com utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. soulcams.com encrypts the information that you provided. 

In addition, soulcams.com does everything to protect your information off-line. All employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. soulcams.com employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties. 

**       Cookies: **

   A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. soulcams.com employs "cookie" technology. We use Cookie to store personal data, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purposes, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate. 

**       Children: **

    soulcams.com does not request, or knowingly collect, personal data from anyone under the age of 18. Furthermore, soulcams.com does not knowingly give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our web site. 

**       Correction/Updating Personal Information: **

   You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to: 

   Administrator   
   Consumer Service Department   
   e-mail: [support@wildorchidz.com](mailto:support@wildorchidz.com "support@wildorchidz.com")

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the above address.
